We will explain this time, too.
Happy New Year!
Going back to the new year...
I've never done it.
Today, we're going to borrow the space
of the kimayaya and play tag.
I'll just go ahead.
Today, we're going to play tag.
Do you know the official rules of tag?
Stand up!
Please pay attention!
Please!
The rules of tag are that the person
who loses will be drawn on the face.
Today, you'll be drawn on the face by
one person who gets one point out of
ten.
If you lose, you'll be drawn on the
face of the person who gets one point.
I thought there was no advantage for
the person who gets one point.
So, I'll eat the super rare part of the
whale.
I'm glad.
But, it's not enough.
So, you'll have to eat only one part.
Can I eat that much?
Because it's precious.
It's a super rare part.
If you eat it, the owner will be
serious.
Are you always serious?
I'm serious.
Yes.
She's serious.
What do you want to say?
I've been living with a blue board in
my right hand since I was born.
I can't lose.
I've been living with sunglasses in my
right hand since I was born.
Please watch again.
I'm not going to exercise, but I'll do
my best.
Let's do it.
I'll do my best.
Will you give me a high five?
I'm going to eat it.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
We will show you our performance.
She is so cute.
She is so sleepy.
She is a foreign woman.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'm so sleepy.
You're still cute.
Wow!
It stinks!
Yay!
I'm going to do it.
Rina-chan is good at studying, so I
want to teach her.
Has just started.
Thank you for watching!
I don't know what to do with this.
I don't like this.
I don't like this wind.
It hurts.
Let's go.
OK.
It's hard.
Please subscribe to my channel.
You are still cute.
Please go home.
I want you to go home.
You are really smelly.
Please go home.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to do it.
It smells.
It's everywhere.
I'm going to put it under your nose.
Don't do that.
Maybe I can clip it and fix it.
I did it!
I don't want to smell more than this.
My nose is close to the camera.
I can smell it.
Are you doing it with a mask?
No.
I can't concentrate.
Look this way.
I want to have a smell channel on
YouTube.
Stretch your nose.
I can't.
I can't stretch it.
Fall down.
Do you want to go?
No.
I don't want to.
I'll put it in a different place.
Look this way.
I'm getting used to it.
It's invincible.
It's gross.
I'm getting used to it.
It's invincible.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm serious.
It's 8 to 3 now.
You have to score less than 10 points.
So, you two will score less than 10
points.
Yes.
I'm ready.
Thank you for watching.
Oh!
You moved!
Wait, it's not over yet.
It's not over yet.
I got it.
I won't do it there.
I'll do it down there.
She's doing it.
OK.
Please watch again.
I'm going to do it. My nose is high.
Thank you
Let's continue
From there?
Yes
Ready?
Aaaaaaaah
No
I'm done
Close your eyes
What?
I can't see your face
Close your eyes
Wait a minute
Look this way
Don't run away
It was a 20-point shot, but I think
it's okay to have 10 points because my
face is buried.
After all, I can't speak
to make it 20.
So, it was a New Year's tree and a
basket board, but how was it?
It was really fun.
It was fun.
I can't speak.
It was fun. I want to do it again.
I want to do it.
Do you want to do it now?
See you tomorrow.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
It's cute.
Don't shake your hand with that face.
Yeah!
Oh, I can eat it.
I can eat it. I forgot.
I'm greedy.
I got it.
You can eat it.
It smells.
Let's get ready to eat.
Yes.
Please wait.
I was waiting.
I came to Hagoita Cafe.
I prepared the special part of Hagoita
Cafe,
which is the famous whale.
Please sit down.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry.
I put too much on my face.
It looks like soap.
I'll put it on my arm.
I'm sorry.
I'm a newbie.
Thank you for watching this video.
This is a super rare part.
It's a high-class meat that you can't
eat easily.
Please enjoy it.
I'll enjoy it.
I'm nervous.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to eat it.
I want to eat it.
Eat it.
I didn't mean to make you eat it.
Oh, I see.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm so happy.
I want to eat.
It's delicious.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's really good.
I'm so disappointed.
Can you tell me what it tastes like?
I can't.
I can't tell unless I eat it.
It's soft.
It melts in my mouth.
Can you ask her again?
I'll ask her.
Are you sure?
Yes.
She's asking again.
I can't tell.
What??
You should eat this.
I want to eat it.
I want to move again.
But today, we only prepared one person.
It's New Year's Day.
I got a bite.
My jaw is stuck.
Thank you for the meal.
It was really delicious.
I can't get it off yet.
Today, we prepared a plate of agoita
and drew on the face.
I came to the store, so I thought I'd
eat it.
It's a great thing.
It's a dish that you can't eat.
I think it's hard to talk.
Fujikami, please finish it.
I got it.
Today, I had a plate of agoita.
I was very happy to play with Rine.
I can't speak because my tongue and jaw
are stuck.
Thank you for preparing such a
wonderful part.
I look forward to working with you this
year.
That's all.
It was Tiwani and Bonjo Akemi.
I'm going to sleep.
Please register your channel.